ctguntalk.com 2014-05-19

# CTGUNTALK.COM Forum's Privacy Policy

[   
](mailto:admin@ctguntalk.com?subject=Advertising)[](https://s3.amazonaws.com/com.alexa.toolbar/atbp/bmWuZ3/download/index.htm)   

| 

###  CTGUNTALK.COM Forum's Privacy Policy 

**CTGUNTALK.COM Forum Privacy Policy Statement**

This Privacy Policy Statement describes how the Forum handles personal information that it receives through this Web site.   
Throughout this Statement, “we” and “us” refer to the CTGUNTALK.COM Forum.

 **Information Collection and Use**  
 **Registration**  
Registration is not necessary for the public to use this Web site. However, members must register in order to gain access to the “members only” portion of the Web site and to subscribe to specific working groups and features. During registration, you must complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give us contact information. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. The CTGUNTALK Forum is the sole owner of the information collected on this Web site.

 **Member Billing**  
In connection with applications for membership and membership billing, we collect contact information and financial information. We use this information for billing purposes and to process your membership application. If we have trouble processing your application or your billing instructions, we will use this information to contact you.

 **Controlled Materials**  
In certain instances, you may only obtain materials or information from this Web site if you provide contact information and other personally identifiable information. We use this information to identify who is receiving these materials and how they are being used. Uses of Information Communications from the Web Site.

 **Generally**   
We use the personally identifiable information we receive to provide member services to you by, for example, setting up working group subscriptions that you select, delivering member newsletters to you, and providing you with information about developments and events that we believe will be of interest to our members. You may subscribe or unsubscribe from each group at any time in order to control your receipt of working group communications. You may not unsubscribe from “all-members” communications as we use this channel of communication to provide information and materials that are necessary for membership.

 **Customer Service**  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

 **Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable) We may elect to share aggregated demographic information about our user base for purposes that support and promote the CTGUNTALK Forum’s mission. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

 **Personally identifiable information**  
We do NOT disclose personally identifiable information of our members, namely their contact information, to other members for any reason. We do not share personally identifiable information with outside third parties. Any and all contact between Vendors, Members and member groups is done from inside the Forum via Personal Messaging or Email.

 **Service Providers**  
We use other third parties to provide certain services, such as the hosting and maintenance of our Web site, event registration services, Web-based meetings and other services that we may elect to provide to our members. Some of these services are provided through the use of CTGUNTALK Forum-branded or co-branded Web pages located on the service providers’ Web sites, which means that certain information you provide to the CTGUNTALK Forum in connection with requested services will be delivered and stored on the service providers’ servers. When you sign up for specific services, or as required in connection with Web site hosting, maintenance and operation, we will share only that personally identifiable information that is necessary for the third party to provide the services. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

 **Legal Disclaimer**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

 **Log Files**  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information and we do not provide it to third parties.

 **Cookies and Clear GIFs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**  
A “cookie” is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. Our Web site analytics software, which analyzes traffic to our Web site and each user’s interaction with our Web site, uses a combination of log files and cookies to provide us with analytical information that we use to improve the efficiency of our Web site in an effort to improve user experience. We do not seek to link this information to personal information about specific users and do not provide this information to third parties. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by the CTGUNTALK Forum Web site only.

 **Links to Other Sites**  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by the CTGUNTALK Forum. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. Member and Public Forums: Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms/Blogs Members of working groups have access to mechanism for posting or distributing messages to other members of their groups. In addition, we may elect to provide bulletin board, chat room or blog functionality on our Web site from time to time. If you use any of these forums, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

 **Access to Personally Identifiable Information**  
As a member, if your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct or update it by making changes to your member profile by logging in and going to your Profile page.

 **Security**  
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at: [admin@ctguntalk.com](mailto:admin@ctguntalk.com). Changes in this Privacy Statement If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

 **Contact Us**  
 **If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:[admin@ctguntalk.com](mailto:admin@ctguntalk.com).**
